{"rows":[{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"جامعة ينويورك أبو ظبي تقع في جزيرة السعديات، عند المخرج ١١","english-question":"What is the exact address of the NYUAD campus?","english-answer":"NYUAD is located in Abu Dhabi, Saadiyat Marina District, at Exit 11","arabic-question":"أين تقع جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي؟","index":2,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1b","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554556"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1b","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554556"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":" توفر جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي ٢٢ تخصصًا في الفنون و الآداب، الهندسة، العلوم، و العلوم الاجتماعية","english-question":"How many majors does NYUAD offer?","english-answer":"NYUAD offers 22 majors across Arts and Humanities, Engineering, Science, and Social Science.","arabic-question":"ما هي التخصصات التي توفرها جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي؟","index":3,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1c","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554557"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1c","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554557"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي توفر بكالوريوس الآداب، بكالوريوس العلوم، و الدكتوراة في بعض التخصصات","english-question":"What degrees does NYUAD offer?","english-answer":"NYUAD offers bachelor of science, bachelor of arts, and a PhD in a selected number of fields","arabic-question":"ما هي الشهادات التي توفرها جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي ؟","index":4,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1d","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554558"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1d","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554558"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"تمثل جماعة نيويورك و جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي و جامعة نيويورك شانغهاي أساس الشبكة العالمية لجامعة نيويورك المكونة من الجامعات و المراكز الأكاديمية لجامعة نيويورك الممتدة في ستة قارات","english-question":"What is the global university?","english-answer":"NYU New York, NYU Abu Dhabi, and NYU Shanghai form the backbone of NYU’s global network of degree granting campuses and academic centers across six continents","arabic-question":"ما هي الجامعة العالمية ؟ ","index":5,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1e","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554559"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1e","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554559"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"رئيس جامعة نيويورك الحالي هو أندرو هاملتون","english-question":"Who is the current president of New York University?","english-answer":"Andrew Hamilton is the current president of New York University","arabic-question":"من هو رئيس جامعة نيويورك الحالي؟ ","index":6,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1f","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554510"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1f","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554510"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"هناك أندية طلابية في جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي و تسمى بمجموعات الاهتمامات الطلابية","english-question":"Are there student clubs at NYUAD?","english-answer":"There are student clubs at NYUAD; they are called Student Interest Groups (SIGs)","arabic-question":"هل هناك أندية طلابية في جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي ؟ ","index":7,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1g","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554511"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1g","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554511"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"على جميع الطلاب المتقدمين إلى أي من فروع جامعة نيويورك تقديم طبل التقديم العام","english-question":"How do students apply to NYUAD","english-answer":"The Common Application is required for students applying to any or all of NYU's three degree-granting campuses in New York, Abu Dhabi, or Shanghai","arabic-question":"كيف يتم التقديم على جامعة نيويورك أبو ظبي ؟ ","index":8,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1h","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554512"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1h","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554512"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"الصفوف في جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي صغيرة نسبياً. تتراوح معظم الصفوف ما بين ۱۰ و ۳۰ طالب. ","english-question":"How large are the class sizes at NYUAD?","english-answer":"Classes at NYU Abu Dhabi are relatively small. Most classes range between 10 and 30 students.","arabic-question":"ما مدى حجم الصفوف في جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي؟","index":9,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1i","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554513"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1i","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554513"}},{"key":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1a","doc":{"arabic-answer":"‬لا يتطلب على الطلاب اختيار تخصصاتهم إلا بعد فصلهم الثالث‫.","english-question":"Do I have to decide my major before coming to NYUAD? ","english-answer":"Students at NYUAD need to declare their majors only by the end of their third semester.","arabic-question":"هل علي اختيار تخصصي قبل القدوم إلى جامعة نيويورك أبوظبي؟","index":10,"language":"English","_id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1j","_rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554514"},"id":"16a41b8cddc767f444e773b3582a6d1j","value":{"rev":"3-f448a5b13e182f3a54314a6ed1554514"}}]}
